{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1590,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":12,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Who Are You? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz to test your knowledge.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si19016","si19034","Text_Caption_106","Image_185"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_148","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  March is Fraud Month.  One of the most well-known cases of fraud was the offer from the Nigerian Prince who was asking you: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"To allow him to come live with you, escaping a plot against the royal family  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To allow him to come live with you, escaping a plot against the royal family \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"To act as an emissary for him to request asylum  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To act as an emissary for him to request asylum \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"To allow him to use your bank account to deposit funds ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To allow him to use your bank account to deposit funds\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23460","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"To allow him to use your identity for the transfer of information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To allow him to use your identity for the transfer of information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: C  While this is very well-known, people are still being lured into surrendering money for the promise of depositing millions (of which they keep a portion).  The ‘alleged’ fees keep increasing for various reasons, so much so that some victims have gone to Nigeria to recover their funds.  Removing large sums in this manner violates section 419 of the Nigerian criminal code; so not only do they lose large sums of money but may end up in a Nigerian prison over a code ‘419 Fraud’ violation.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer: C  While this is very well-known, people are still being lured into surrendering money for the promise of depositing millions (of which they keep a portion).  The ‘alleged’ fees keep increasing for various reasons, so much so that some victims have gone to Nigeria to recover their funds.  Removing large sums in this manner violates section 419 of the Nigerian criminal code; so not only do they lose large sums of money but may end up in a Nigerian prison over a code ‘419 Fraud’ violation.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_148","si12349","si12364","si12386","si20589","si23464","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  March is Fraud Month.  One of the most well-known cases of fraud was the offer from the Nigerian Prince who was asking you:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_782","roles":{}},{"id":"si23513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_755","title":"2.  What is the investor scam that paid early ‘profits’ to their investors from the funds of new investors, not actually making any real income? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23528","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_771","title":"The Enron Scheme ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23524_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_413","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Enron Scheme\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23535","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_772","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23539","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"The Charles Ponzi Scheme ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23535_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_414","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Charles Ponzi Scheme\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23550","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"The Multi-level Scheme ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23546_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"415","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Multi-level Scheme\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23557","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23561","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","title":"The Pyramid Scheme ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23557_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"417","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The Pyramid Scheme\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_781","roles":{}},{"id":"si23638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23656","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23696","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23708","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23720","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23744","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23768","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23780","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23792","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23805q1","for":"Slide23805q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23580","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_778","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Charles Ponzi was arrested in 1920 for over 86 counts of mail fraud.  His now famous ‘Ponzi Scheme’ is alive and well and being used by others like Lou Pearlman (founder of the Backstreet Boys and N’ Sync) and Bernie Madoff who ‘made off’ with over $50 Billion!  Ensure you closely investigate every ‘opportunity’ that asks you to surrender your money or confidential information.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23592","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_779","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Charles Ponzi was arrested in 1920 for over 86 counts of mail fraud.  His now famous ‘Ponzi Scheme’ is alive and well and being used by others like Lou Pearlman (founder of the Backstreet Boys and N’ Sync) and Bernie Madoff who ‘made off’ with over $50 Billion!  Ensure you closely investigate every ‘opportunity’ that asks you to surrender your money or confidential information.     Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23604","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_780","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23805","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_193","si23513","si23528","si23539","si23550","si23561","si23638","si23656","si23678","si23696","si23708","si23720","si23732","si23744","si23756","si23768","si23780","si23792","si23604"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23805"},"question":{"interactionId":"23493","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.  What is the investor scam that paid early ‘profits’ to their investors from the funds of new investors, not actually making any real income?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si24292","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_810","roles":{}},{"id":"si24189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_797","title":"3.  The ‘Grandma Scam’ is where someone claiming to be a grandchild contacts a senior citizen in desperate need of money.  How much are senior citizens robbed of each year by scams like these? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_798","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24204","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_799","title":"Approximately $500 Million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24200_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_422","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Approximately $500 Million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24211","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_800","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24215","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_801","title":"Roughly $7.5 Million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24211_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_423","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Roughly $7.5 Million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24222","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24226","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_803","title":"Eighty million dollars ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24222_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"415_424","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Eighty million dollars\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24233","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_804","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_805","title":"Estimated $3 Billion ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24233_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"417_425","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Estimated $3 Billion\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24286","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_809","roles":{}},{"id":"si24314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24332","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24354","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24372","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_127","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24384","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24396","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24408","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24420","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24432","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24444","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24456","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24468","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24481q2","for":"Slide24481q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24256","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_806","title":"Correct - Answer: D  Sadly, it is estimated that 3 billion dollars are stolen from senior citizens each year in scams.  AARP explains that even well-educated seniors (doctors and lawyers) have fallen prey to this scam as it reaches them on an emotional level.  Discuss scams like this with senior citizens you may know, particularly those within your family.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_807","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  Sadly, it is estimated that 3 billion dollars are stolen from senior citizens each year in scams.  AARP explains that even well-educated seniors (doctors and lawyers) have fallen prey to this scam as it reaches them on an emotional level.  Discuss scams like this with senior citizens you may know, particularly those within your family.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24280","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_808","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24481","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_195","si24189","si24204","si24215","si24226","si24237","si24314","si24332","si24354","si24372","si24384","si24396","si24408","si24420","si24432","si24444","si24456","si24468","si24280"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24481"},"question":{"interactionId":"24169","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  The ‘Grandma Scam’ is where someone claiming to be a grandchild contacts a senior citizen in desperate need of money.  How much are senior citizens robbed of each year by scams like these?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_196","roles":{}},{"id":"si24660","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_826","roles":{}},{"id":"si24546","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"4.  The CRA scam has grown in intensity in the last few years.  According to the RCMP, which of the following will the CRA not do: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24557","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24561","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"Call and threaten you to pay a tax debt  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24557_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_426","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Call and threaten you to pay a tax debt \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24572","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_815","title":"Leave a voice message, text or email advising of a warrant of arrest for a tax debt ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24568_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_427","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Leave a voice message, text or email advising of a warrant of arrest for a tax debt\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24579","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_816","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_817","title":"Request that you pay your tax debt with cryptocurrency such as Bitcoin or gift cards ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24579_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"415_428","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Request that you pay your tax debt with cryptocurrency such as Bitcoin or gift cards\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24590","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_818","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24594","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_819","title":"Have you deported if you do not pay an owed tax debt ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24590_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"417_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Have you deported if you do not pay an owed tax debt\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_820","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24601_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24654","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","roles":{}},{"id":"si24682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_128","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24700","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_129","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24722","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_130","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24740","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_131","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24764","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24776","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24788","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24800","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24812","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24824","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24836","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24849q3","for":"Slide24849q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"Correct - Answer: E  Between September 2018 and January 2019, the RCMP have closed approximately 40 call centres directly related to this scam.  If you suspect a CRA phone scam, hang up the phone immediately and directly contact the CRA if you have questions about your account.  If you are a victim of the scam or have information that might lead to an arrest, report it to the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24636","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"Incorrect - Answer: E  Between September 2018 and January 2019, the RCMP have closed approximately 40 call centres directly related to this scam.  If you suspect a CRA phone scam, hang up the phone immediately and directly contact the CRA if you have questions about your account.  If you are a victim of the scam or have information that might lead to an arrest, report it to the Canadian Anti-Fraud Centre (CAFC).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24648","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24849","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_196","si24546","si24561","si24572","si24583","si24594","si24605","si24682","si24700","si24722","si24740","si24752","si24764","si24776","si24788","si24800","si24812","si24824","si24836","si24648"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24849"},"question":{"interactionId":"24526","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.  The CRA scam has grown in intensity in the last few years.  According to the RCMP, which of the following will the CRA not do:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_796","roles":{}},{"id":"si23851","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_783","title":"5.  Two-factor authentication is becoming increasingly common for accessing  online services, resulting in new a new type of fraud. If you see a text message  such as this on your phone: “Customer Notification/Please update your profile to confirm your identity http://TD-account3517.com”, what should you do (click all that apply)?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_784","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23866","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_785","title":"Click on the link to verify your identity ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23866","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24143q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23862_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Click on the link to verify your identity\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_786","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_787","title":"Ask yourself if your bank has required two-factor authentication for your account ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23877","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24143q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23873_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ask yourself if your bank has required two-factor authentication for your account\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23884","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_788","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_789","title":"Always ignore these messages, they are obviously smishing texts  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23888","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24143q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23884_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Always ignore these messages, they are obviously smishing texts \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23895","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_790","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23899","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_791","title":"If you are unsure, contact your bank to verify ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23899","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24143q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23895_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"If you are unsure, contact your bank to verify\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24493","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ask yourself if there is a reason you are receiving this message (are you in the middle of a transaction that would require it)? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24493","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24143q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si24489_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ask yourself if there is a reason you are receiving this message (are you in the middle of a transaction that would require it)?\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_795","roles":{}},{"id":"si23976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23994","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24046","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24058","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24094","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24106","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24118","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24130","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24143q4","for":"Slide24143q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23918","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_792","title":"Correct - Answers: B, D, E  With two-factor authentication (which many banks are now requiring), you are asked to provide a second way for them to identify you before allowing access to your account.  While this is a good practice, ensure you do not give them a second contact you do not wish them to have (example:  your child’s phone number to send a confirmation text).   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_793","title":"Incorrect - Answers: B, D, E  With two-factor authentication (which many banks are now requiring), you are asked to provide a second way for them to identify you before allowing access to your account.  While this is a good practice, ensure you do not give them a second contact you do not wish them to have (example:  your child’s phone number to send a confirmation text).   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23942","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_794","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24143","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_194","si23851","si23866","si23877","si23888","si23899","si24493","si23976","si23994","si24016","si24034","si24046","si24058","si24070","si24082","si24094","si24106","si24118","si24130","si23942"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24143"},"question":{"interactionId":"23831","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  Two-factor authentication is becoming increasingly common for accessing \ronline services, resulting in new a new type of fraud. If you see a text message \rsuch as this on your phone: “Customer Notification/Please update your profile to confirm your identity http://TD-account3517.com”, what should you do (click all that apply)? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B","D","E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_197","roles":{}},{"id":"si25028","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_842","roles":{}},{"id":"si24914","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_827","title":"6. It you suspect a text is a scam, it is advisable to text them back and let them know that you will be reporting them. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24925","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_828","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24929","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_829","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24925_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24936","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_830","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24940","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_831","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24936_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_841","roles":{}},{"id":"si25050","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_132","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25068","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25090","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25120","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25132","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25156","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25168","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25180","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25204","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25217q5","for":"Slide25217q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_838","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Texting the scammer back may allow them to install malware that can silently collect personal information from your phone.  You may also be charged fees that you are not expecting.  Always be suspicious of ‘unsolicited’ text messages (texts you are not expecting).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_839","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  Texting the scammer back may allow them to install malware that can silently collect personal information from your phone.  You may also be charged fees that you are not expecting.  Always be suspicious of ‘unsolicited’ text messages (texts you are not expecting).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_840","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25217","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_197","si24914","si24929","si24940","si25050","si25068","si25090","si25108","si25120","si25132","si25144","si25156","si25168","si25180","si25192","si25204","si25016"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25217"},"question":{"interactionId":"24894","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6. It you suspect a text is a scam, it is advisable to text them back and let them know that you will be reporting them.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_198","roles":{}},{"id":"si25336","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_852","roles":{}},{"id":"si25255","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_843","title":"7. Online scams have been around as long as the internet and include scams such as Greeting Card Scams, Romance Scams and Fake News Scams.  You can tell an internet scam by the email address of the company. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25266","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_844","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25270","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_845","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25266_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_846","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25281","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_847","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25277_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25330","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_851","roles":{}},{"id":"si25358","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25376","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_137","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_138","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25416","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_139","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25428","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25440","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25452","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25476","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25488","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25500","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25512","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25525q6","for":"Slide25525q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25300","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_848","title":"Correct - Answer: B  False.  A fake email address is one of the easiest things to create.  There are virtually no filters in creating many online provider email accounts and little or no requirement to authenticate your identity.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_849","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  False.  A fake email address is one of the easiest things to create.  There are virtually no filters in creating many online provider email accounts and little or no requirement to authenticate your identity.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25324","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_850","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25525","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_198","si25255","si25270","si25281","si25358","si25376","si25398","si25416","si25428","si25440","si25452","si25464","si25476","si25488","si25500","si25512","si25324"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25525"},"question":{"interactionId":"25235","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. Online scams have been around as long as the internet and include scams such as Greeting Card Scams, Romance Scams and Fake News Scams.  You can tell an internet scam by the email address of the company.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_199","roles":{}},{"id":"si25650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_862","roles":{}},{"id":"si25569","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_853","title":"8. The most susceptible age group for online scams and financial fraud is: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25580","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_854","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25584","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_855","title":"Millennials ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25580_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"432","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Millennials\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si25591","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_856","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25595","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_857","title":"Under 15 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25591_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"434","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Under 15\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25847","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25851","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Senior Citizens ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25847_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Senior Citizens\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25862","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ages 35 - 55 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25862_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ages 35 - 55\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25644","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_861","roles":{}},{"id":"si25672","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_140","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25690","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_141","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25712","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_142","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25730","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_143","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25742","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25754","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25766","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25778","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25814","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25826","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25839q7","for":"Slide25839q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25614","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_858","title":"Correct - Answer: A  Surprised?  When you think about it, millennials are the group that spend more of their time online, whether gaming, surfing the web, looking at YouTube or texting.  The average affluent person in the 18  34 year old age group spends approximately 53 hours per week online and are prolific users of social media.  Seniors, however, tend to lose more money per incident than millennials.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25626","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_859","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  Surprised?  When you think about it, millennials are the group that spend more of their time online, whether gaming, surfing the web, looking at YouTube or texting.  The average affluent person in the 18  34 year old age group spends approximately 53 hours per week online and are prolific users of social media.  Seniors, however, tend to lose more money per incident than millennials.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_860","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25839","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_199","si25569","si25584","si25595","si25851","si25866","si25672","si25690","si25712","si25730","si25742","si25754","si25766","si25778","si25790","si25802","si25814","si25826","si25638"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25839"},"question":{"interactionId":"25549","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. The most susceptible age group for online scams and financial fraud is:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_200","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_200","roles":{}},{"id":"si26018","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_876","roles":{}},{"id":"si25915","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_863","title":"9.  One of the newest ‘popularity contests’ is how many friends you have on social media.  This is a safe way for your child to build their self esteem. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_864","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25930","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_865","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25926_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"432_435","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25937","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_866","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25941","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_867","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25937_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"434_436","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26012","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_875","roles":{}},{"id":"si26040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_144","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_145","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_146","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26098","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_147","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26122","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26134","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26146","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26158","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26170","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26182","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26194","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26207q8","for":"Slide26207q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25982","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_872","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  With social media scams and cybercriminals looking for any way to gain your personal information, the more friends you have, the more compromised you are likely to be.  With hundreds of ‘friends’ it is nearly impossible to know who all of them are.  Explain this to social media users in your family and remind them that “the safest user is a skeptical user”.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25994","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_873","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  With social media scams and cybercriminals looking for any way to gain your personal information, the more friends you have, the more compromised you are likely to be.  With hundreds of ‘friends’ it is nearly impossible to know who all of them are.  Explain this to social media users in your family and remind them that “the safest user is a skeptical user”.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26006","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_874","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26207","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_200","si25915","si25930","si25941","si26040","si26058","si26080","si26098","si26110","si26122","si26134","si26146","si26158","si26170","si26182","si26194","si26006"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26207"},"question":{"interactionId":"25895","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"9.  One of the newest ‘popularity contests’ is how many friends you have on social media.  This is a safe way for your child to build their self esteem.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_120","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_121","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"  Stay Current With   Information Security   By Subscribing to the    Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Image_121","Button_4","si19054","si19068","Text_Caption_5","SmartShape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"March2019Quiz","class":"project","title":"March2019Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide12483","Slide23805","Slide24481","Slide24849","Slide24143","Slide25217","Slide25525","Slide25839","Slide26207","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide23805q1","Slide24481q2","Slide24849q3","Slide24143q4","Slide25217q5","Slide25525q6","Slide25839q7","Slide26207q8"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":90,"passScore":72}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide23805","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide24481","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide24849","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide24143","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide25217","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide25525","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25839","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide26207","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 12"}]}